servecounterstrike.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy - No-IP

### We do not disclose personal data to unaffiliated third parties.

Except as expressly described in this Policy, No-IP.com does not disclose customers' personal data, including email addresses, to unaffiliated third parties. We do collect, use, and permit our affiliates and partners to use, customer data for several purposes, which are discussed in detail below.

## How Do We Collect and Use Information?

### Registration Information

Our site's registration area requires customers to supply contact Information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic Information, such as your ZIP code, age, or income level. We use this Information to send you promotional materials from our company and from some of our partners. However, users may opt out of -- or opt in to -- these promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.)

### Demographic Information

We also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at No-IP.com. Based on this Information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you.

### Order Information

When you place an order, No-IP.com requests Information such as contact Information, credit card number and demographic Information. The contact Information you provide is used to send you orders, company Information and promotional material from our partners. You can opt out or opt in at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Your financial Information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. Demographic data is collected to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would interest you most. 

### Online Survey Information

To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and demographic Information. No-IP.com uses this data to send you Information about the company. We might use this Information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would most interest you.

### Information Collected In Contests

To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic Information. No-IP.com uses this data to send you Information about the company. We might use this Information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data are collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you.

### IP Address & User Activity

We, or the third parties who perform services on our behalf, collect IP address, log data, and other related Information about how users access and use our site and services. This Information may be used for several reasons, including to provide our services to you, to process your requests or orders, to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, to help identify you or your shopping cart, to gather broad demographic Information, to investigate, prevent or take action against actual or suspected violations of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, for other security purposes, and for other purposes as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Public Forums Guidelines

No-IP.com may offer chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that Information that is disclosed in these arenas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal Information.

## Do We Automatically Collect Any Information?

Yes, when you interact with our Web site or use our services we want your experience to be easy, meaningful and safe. We or third parties we have engaged may collect certain non-personally identifiable data, such as your IP address, browser type and certain log data about how users use our Site and Services, using cookies and other tracking technologies. 

This enables us to better understand how users use our site and services, so that we can improve our Site and services, personalize your experience at the Site, analyze and better understand usage patterns, and for other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For more Information see the "IP Address and User Activity" section above. We do not combine this Information with the other personally identifiable data we have collected about you.

## Why Do We Disclose Information?

We do not sell your personal data to unaffiliated third parties so that they may send you marketing or promotional Information. However, we may disclose customer data, including personal data, that we have collected as described below:

### In Response to Legal Process

No-IP.com may disclose any personally identifiable or non-personally customer data, in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process. 

### Protection Of No-IP.com & Network Security

We may disclose, or permit the disclosure of, any customer data, in order to protect the rights and property of No-IP.com, or to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding actual or suspected illegal activities, fraud, potential threats to the safety of any person, or actual or suspected violations of this Policy or our Terms & Conditions. 

### Aggregate Or Anonymous Information

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we may share aggregate, anonymous, or de-identified Information about customers with third parties for marketing, advertising, research, analysis or similar purposes; however, we do not disclose personally-identifiable data to such third parties.

## How Do We Secure Your Personal Information?

No-IP.com features security measures 128-bit SSL encryption to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of Information placed under our control.

## What Else Should You Know?

### Children's Guidelines

We do not knowingly collect or use any personally identifiable Information from children. 

### Opt Out / Opt In

No-IP.com allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can send e-mail to a remove mailing list.

### Modification Of This Policy

No-IP.com may amend or modify this privacy policy at any time upon written notice from No-IP.com to customers. In the event of an amendment, No-Ip.com will provide an opportunity for customers to opt out of the new policy, either by email or by filling out a form on the No-IP.com website. 

### Correct / Update Personal Information 

No-IP.com allows you to change or modify your personal Information by sending e-mail to a remove e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page.

### Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites. No-IP.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

Please [contact us](https://www.noip.com/contact) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
